

Experience in developing projects across various fields, such as market analytics and a search engine for companies, which I have used as part of my learning process (learning through real application).

Database work on an international project (lived in Dublin). There, I enhanced my communication skills across international teams.

Teamwork has been an integral part of my learning and professional journey from the beginning.

I consistently maintain a holistic **view** of projects, going beyond the technological aspects.

LANGUAGES

- Spanish (Native)
- Catalan (Native)
- English (B2 Level)
- oriol@oriolfontcuberta.dev
- linkedin.com/in/oriolfontcuberta
- +34 644-33-53-45
- oriolfontcuberta.dev

ORIOL FONTCUBERTA

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER

EXPERIENCE

IT Intern (Internship) **Dublin - Ireland** Mar. 2023 - Jul. 2023

Participated in an Erasmus internship program as part of my Technician in microcomputer systems and networks degree.

Waiter

Menorca - Spain

Aug. 2023 - Sep. 2023

Worked as a summer job, providing excellent customer service, managing orders, and ensuring a pleasant dining experience for guests.

Sports Instructor (Volunteer) Menorca - Spain Jul. 2021 - Aug. 2021

Volunteered with children, organizing and leading sports activities, fostering teamwork, and promoting physical fitness in a fun and engaging way.

EDUCATION

Web Applications Development (HNC) La Salle Gràcia | Sep. 2023 - Current

Technician in microcomputer systems and networks les Joan Ramis | Ramis | 2021 - 2023

PROGRAMMING

- HTML
 - JavaScript
- TypeScript

- CSS
- Java
- Git

- MySQL
- C
- PHP

NodeJS

- Oracle ReactJS
 - **PROJECTS**
- Forex market strategies automation.
- Web Game Front-End (strategy game).